<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ViewPresent</string>
    <string name="introInfo">Do you wish to be a PRESENTER or SPECTATOR?</string>
    <string name="presenter">Presenter</string>
    <string name="spectator">Spectator</string>
    <string name="missingPermission">Insufficient permissions granted</string>
    <string name="startDiscovering">You are now a presenter!</string>
    <string name="startAdvertising">You are now a viewer!</string>
    <string name="username">Please enter a nickname</string>
    <string name="enter">Enter</string>
    <string name="skip">Skip</string>
    <string name="change_username_setting">Change Username</string>
    <string name="change_photo_setting">Change Photo</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="help"><![CDATA[Help & Feedback]]></string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="participants">PARTICIPANTS</string>
    <string name="aboutTextCredits">"This app was created for an internship at the LMU during the summer semester 2018.\n\nIt was developed by: AAAAAA, BBBBBBB, CCCCCC and DDDDDD.\n\nIcons have been obtained from: https://www.iconfinder.com/iconsets/education-flat-7 under the creative common license.
    </string>
    <string name="poke">Poke</string>
    <string name="call">call</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome!</string>
    <string name="dismiss">Dismiss</string>
    <string name="selectDevices">Select devices for file sharing:</string>
    <string name="deselectAll">Deselect all</string>
    <string name="selectAll">Select all</string>
    <string name="noDevicesFound">Noone wants to join your presentation yet :(</string>
    <string name="okay">Okay</string>
    <string name="available_presenters">Subscriptions</string>
    <string name="no_devices_found">No presentations to join...</string>
    <string name="help_feedback">ViewPresent is an app developed for enabling easy and comfortable file transfer via Bluetooth within a range of approximate 100m.
        \n\nIt does not need any internet connection and allows a fast file transfer between multiple nearby devices.
        \n\nThere are two main role types in this application: “Presenters” and “Viewers”.
        \nPresenters are allowed to distribute files or data to all subscribed devices (viewers).
        \nThey will automatically search for nearby devices (viewers) and can then select what devices he actually wishes or does not wish to include in the file sharing group.
        \nA viewer therefore is somebody who subscribed to a presenter, allowing him to receive everything the presenter distributes.
        \nViewers can subscribe to multiple presenters, and presenters can have multiple viewers.
        \n\nIf a viewer is allowed to receive data from one or multiple presenters, he can then also select all the devices he eventually wants to subscribe to.
        \n\nFor for any concerns or feedback, please contact us under xxxxxx@campus.lmu.de
</string>
</resources>
